Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65, 1872-1976
6374 PUBS
Brown University Library
77.8 linear ft.
Publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Archives Union File Part 2 is a collection of printed ephemeral documents, issued primarily by trade unions and labor organizations.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into three sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-65
Section 2: Boxes 66-129
Section 3: Boxes 130-143
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
Subjects:
American Federation of Railroad Workers; Associated Industries f Massachusetts; Association of Catholic Trade Unionists (ACTU); Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association; Bartenders International League of America; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (BLE); Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (BLF&E); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT); Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Agents (BRAC); Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters; Building Service Employees' International Union; Chase Bank Club of New York; Chicago Federation of Labor; Council of Europe; Hotel and Restaurant Employes International Alliance; International Association of Car Workers; International Association of Machinists (AIM); International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW); International Brotherhood of Paper Makers; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU); International Seamen's Union of America; International Union of Steam Engineers; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW); Journeymen Tailors' Union of America; Labor Record; Labour Party; Manufacturers' Record Publishing Company; National Association of Manufacturers; National Manufacturers Company; National Metal Trades Association; New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA); Order of Railroad Telegraphers (ORC); S. P. Dinsmore and Co.; Sailors' Union of the Pacific; Service Employees International Union (SEIU); Standard Oil Company; Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA); The National Underwriter Company; Transport Union of America (TUA); Transport Workers Union of America; U.S. President's Commission on the Status of Women; United Brotherhood of Leather Workers on Horse Goods; United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes; United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes and Railway Shop Laborers; United Garment Workers of America; United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Works International Union; United Leather Workers International Union; United Nations; United Office and Professional Workers of America; United Papermakers and Paperworkers; United Steelworkers of America (USWA)
Form and Genre Terms:
Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF)
5583: Archives Organization File (AOF)
5583 AV: Archives Organization File (AOF) Audio-Visual Materials
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5956: Archives Organization File Additional Records
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
6374 PUBS: Archives Union File Part 2
6374 PUBS: Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
6374 PUBS: Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143
CONTAINER LIST
- American Industries, 1907-1908 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: National Manufacturers Company
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1907: Aug.)
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1907: Sept.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1907: Sept.)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1907: Oct.)
  - Item 5: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1907: Oct.)
  - Item 6: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1907: Nov.)
  - Item 7: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1907: Nov.)
  - Item 8: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.8 (1907: Dec.)
  - Item 9: American Industries, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (1907: Dec.)
  - Item 10: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.10 (1908: Jan.)
  - Item 11: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.11 (1908: Jan.)
  - Item 12: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.12 (1908: Feb.)
- American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1908: Feb.)
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1908: Mar.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1908: Mar.)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1908: Apr.)
  - Item 5: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1908: Apr.)
  - Item 6: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (1908: May)
  - Item 7: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.7 (1908: May)
  - Item 8: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.8 (1908: June)
  - Item 9: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1908: July)
  - Item 10: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.11 (1908: July)
  - Item 11: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.12 (1908: Aug.)
- American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1908: Aug.)
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1908: Oct.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1908: Sept. 1)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1908; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1908: Sept. 15)
- American Industries, 1909-1910 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: National Association of Manufacturers
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (1909: Aug.)
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.2 (1909: Sept.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.3 (1909: Oct.)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.4 (1909: Nov.)
  - Item 5: American Industries, 1909; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.5 (1909: Dec.)
  - Item 6: American Industries, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.6 (1910: Jan.)
  - Item 7: American Industries, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.7 (1910: Feb.)
  - Item 8: American Industries, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.8 (1910: Mar.)
  - Item 9: American Industries, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.9 (1910: Apr.)
  - Item 10: American Industries, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.10 (1910: May)
  - Item 11: American Industries, 1910; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.11 (1910: June)
- American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15:no.6 (1915: Jan.)
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15:no.7 (1915: Feb.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15:no.8 (1915: Mar.)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15:no.9 (1915: Apr.)
  - Item 5: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15:no.10 (1915: May)
  - Item 6: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15:no.11 (1915: June)
  - Item 7: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.15:no.12 (1915: July)
- American Industries, 1915-1916 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.1 (1915: Aug.)
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.2 (1915: Sept.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.3 (1915: Oct.)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.4 (1915: Nov.)
  - Item 5: American Industries, 1915; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.5 (1915: Dec.)
  - Item 6: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.6 (1916: Jan.)
  - Item 7: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.7 (1916: Feb.)
  - Item 8: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.8 (1916: Mar.)
  - Item 9: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.9 (1916: Apr.)
  - Item 10: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.10 (1916: May)
  - Item 11: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.11 (1916: June)
  - Item 12: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.16:no.12 (1916: July)
- American Industries, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1916: Aug.)
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.2 (1916: Sept.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.3 (1916: Oct.)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.4 (1916: Nov.)
  - Item 5: American Industries, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.5 (1916: Dec.)
  - Item 6: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.6 (1917: Jan.)
  - Item 7: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.7 (1917: Feb.)
  - Item 8: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.8 (1917: Mar.)
  - Item 9: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.10 (1917: May)
  - Item 10: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.11 (1917: June)
  - Item 11: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.17:no.12 (1917: July)
- American Industries, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.1 (1917: Aug.)
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.2 (1917: Sept.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.3 (1917: Oct.)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.4 (1917: Nov.)
  - Item 5: American Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.5 (1917: Dec.)
  - Item 6: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.6 (1918: Jan.)
  - Item 7: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.7 (1918: Feb.)
  - Item 8: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.8 (1918: Mar.)
  - Item 9: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.9 (1918: Apr.)
  - Item 10: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.10 (1918: May)
  - Item 11: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.11 (1918: June)
  - Item 12: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.18:no.12 (1918: July)
- American Industries, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.1 (1918: Aug.)
  - Item 2: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.2 (1918: Sept.)
  - Item 3: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.3 (1918: Oct.)
  - Item 4: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.4 (1918: Nov.)
  - Item 5: American Industries, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.5 (1918: Dec.)
  - Item 6: American Industries, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.6 (1919: Jan.)
  - Item 7: American Industries, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.7 (1919: Feb.)
  - Item 8: American Industries, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.8 (1919: Mar.)
  - Item 9: American Industries, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.9 (1919: Apr.)
  - Item 10: American Industries, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.10 (1919: May)
  - Item 11: American Industries, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.11 (1919: June)
  - Item 12: American Industries, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.19:no.12 (1919: July)
- Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
    Notes: v.42:no.1 (1907: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.2 (1907: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.3 (1907: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.4 (1907: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.5 (1907: May)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.42:no.6 (1907: June)
- Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.1 (1907: July)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.2 (1907: Aug.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.3 (1907: Sept.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.4 (1907: Oct.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.5 (1907: Nov.)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1907; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.43:no.6 (1907: Dec.)
- Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.1 (1909: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.2 (1909: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.3 (1909: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.4 (1909: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.5 (1909: May)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1909; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.46:no.6 (1909: June)
- Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen
    Notes: v.38:no.1 (1905: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.38:no.2 (1905: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.38:no.3 (1905: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.38:no.4 (1905: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.38:no.5 (1905: May)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.38:no.6 (1905: June)
- Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.39:no.1 (1905: July)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.39:no.2 (1905: Aug.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.39:no.3 (1905: Sept.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.39:no.4 (1905: Oct.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.39:no.5 (1905: Nov.)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1905; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.39:no.6 (1905: Dec.)
- Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.40:no.1 (1906: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.40:no.2 (1906: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.40:no.3 (1906: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.40:no.4 (1906: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.40:no.5 (1906: May)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.40:no.6 (1906: June)
- Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.41:no.1 (1906: July)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.41:no.2 (1906: Aug.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.41:no.3 (1906: Sept.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.41:no.4 (1906: Oct.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.41:no.5 (1906: Nov.)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1906; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.41:no.6 (1906: Dec.)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes
    Notes: v.41:no.1 (1932: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.2 (1932: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.3 (1932: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.4 (1932: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.5 (1932: May)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.6 (1932: June)
  - Item 7: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.7 (1932: July)
  - Item 8: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.8 (1932: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.9 (1932: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.10 (1932: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.11 (1932: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.41:no.12 (1932: Dec.)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.1 (1933: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.2 (1933: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.3 (1933: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.4 (1933: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.5 (1933: May)
  - Item 6: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.6 (1933: June)
  - Item 7: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.7 (1933: July)
  - Item 8: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.8 (1933: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.9 (1933: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.10 (1933: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.11 (1933: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.42:no.12 (1933: Dec.)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.43:no.1 (1934: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.43:no.2 (1934: Feb.)